seasportstv.com 2018-12-22

# Bollywood Charcha

## **Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting SeaSportstv’s privacy and services section we value your trust in us. We want to give you clear idea about what information we collect and how we use it. In general, submission of your personal information is not at all required in order to browse Sportz247, you can surf this site without revealing any of your personal info.

**Information we collect-**

In case you connect with SeaSportstv via social networking sites like Facebook, Twitter, Google+ etc we can store your personal information you have chosen to display in that networks. Further, in case you can send or receive personal messages to other user of SeaSportstv we can record all messages that you send or receive.

**Note:**  We respect our visitors/users rights and support “Right to be forgotten”. If you think you’ve ever shared your contact details with us & want us to remove that info, please contact us at _…_

**What About IP addresses?**

We may use your personal information or data we collect in connection with your use of SeaSportstv in order to implement, prevent, investigate, identity theft, fraud, or multiple accounts to prevent making abusive comments. In order to get such information we may collect data like IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), which browser you are using to visit SeaSportstv.com like Google chrome plus we also capture time taken by you to surf on SeaSportstv and the number of pages you visited on the site.

**Sharing and use of personal information-**

We use industry’s best standard measures to protect your personal information in our database but we cannot control over the other users with whom you share your user profile and information.

We may use the user information:-

  * In order to improve our content and information.
  * To develop new content.
  * To rectify the correct info or content given on the site, if any

However we do not disclose your personal information to others without your approval or in occurrence of some specific incidents:-

  * In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation against the our terms and provisions
  * To enforce or imply terms and conditions and privacy policies
  * To protect our reputation, property and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users
  * If fake information is provided and fraud is detected, the details will be given to graud prevention agencies.
  * In case of transferring or selling the website to other company so user’s info will be transferred too. We may disclose non-identifiable data to third parties which doesn’t include your name, email address or contact number.
  * We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law to do so in a good belief because it is necessary to disclose such info to counter court orders or miscellaneous legal processes.

**Cookies:**

When you use your browser in order to visit or surf any website usually a small text files can take place in your computer as browser’s history or program data subfolders which is called as ‘Cookie’. Cookie can be of two types- one which expires when you close the browser and another is which stays on your computer until you delete them manually. Some cookies are important to download certain information from the website, so like another companies our readers will get cookies by us or by companies which are running their ads on our website. Cookies can help us and advertisers to analyze and identify users on our website and it also helps us to serve content to match your preferences.

**Policy updation:**

In any case if we make change or update our private policy or its provisions we will inform you by posting on our page/website.
